Antonio Guedes

Project Management & Sales Leader

PROFESSIONAL & PERSONAL PROFILE

I am incredibly passionate about genuine mentorship with more than 6 years' experience working at the forefront of Project Management & Sales. Holding critical leadership positions, I aspire to create sustainable & authentic work environments through a focus on strategic people initiatives. Additionally, leading numerous projects has led me to serve as a consultant to organisations, customers and internal personnel on project management and customer service. I also have an avid passion for combining community values to my own professionally.

Finally, I am a principled person at heart... balancing my responsibilities with my family with my responsibilities professionally, I embed the highest amount of integrity and dignity in everything I do.



0450 628 249



gguedesantonio@gmail.com



Sydney, NSW, 2000

in

linkedin.com/in/antonio-guedes-3198997b

Education

Civil Engineering Bachelor I Federal University of Minas Gerais I 2010 – 2015

Language Skills

English I Full professional proficiency

Portuguese I Native proficiency

Spanish I Limited working proficiency

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

PRODUCTION I SYDNEY METRO OPERATIONS

Hanson | Hymix (HeidelbergCement Group) | 2018 – Present

Accountable for effectively leading the entire Sydney Metro Production Operations end to end, through the creation & implementation of a strategic plan whilst overseeing a production budget of upwards of \$2.9Mil and producing up to 200k M3 of ready mix concrete per year on. Further to this, I am responsible for managing all quality control and customer service, doing so through education, influence and leadership; I drive initiatives through relationships and building trust by keeping customer satisfaction as a core value, proactively delivering engagement strategies to champion change.

Finally, I am accountable for the authentic leadership & development of a team of approximately 40 people. My leadership style is best described as genuine, empathic and compassionate, driving people to be better, holding them accountable for their own standards and those around them.

SALES I MANAGEMENT DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM I EASTERN REGION

Hanson | Hymix (HeidelbergCement Group) | 2017 - 2018

The two-year, rotational Management Development Program, combines internal and external management, leadership and technical education with on-the-job experience across a range of functions and operations. Some of the business areas I was exposed as a HeidelbergCement Group graduate were:

- -Quarry Management at the Sancrox hard rock quarry where I improved the WHS and environmental compliance. Further to this, also improving the revenue by creating a new product and introducing it on the local market.
- -Production management at Hanson Byron Bay and Hymix Pyrmont concrete plants, by implementing the new SAP plant maintenance system. Getting a better average life of assets through proactive maintenance and efficient budgetary control.
- -Customer Service and Logistics at the Brisbane CSC where by connecting different logistics stakeholders I was able to improve Hymix TRIMBLE and TESYS procedures.
- -Sales at the Hymix Sales team based in Sydney. Where I was able to participate on the process of rebranding the Hymix brand to boost tier 2 sales.

Expertise

- Lean Production
- Project Management
- Budget & Resource Management
- Strategic Planning
- Business Continuity Planning
- People Leadership & Coaching
- Customer service
- Quality control
- Maintenance Planning

Professional Development

Negotiation | CMA | 2020

Performance & Productivity I Performance Lab I 2020

Sales is a Science Initiative - SIAS -Core Sales Skills I Heidelberg Cement I 2020

JavaScript Course | Udemy | 2020

Git/Web Developer: Mastering the Modern Workflow I Udemy I 2020

HTML5 and CSS3 | Udemy | 2020

Pearson Test of English - PTE Academic - Total Score: 88/90 I Superior English I 2019

ELP (Emerging Leaders Program) -Culture Driving Innovation I Heidelberg Cement I 2019

Influencing Skills I CMA I 2019

Visible Leadership I 2019

Leadership Conversations I Caterpillar 2018

SAP Workshop I 2018

MS Project | Treinar Minas | 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

PROJECT MANAGER

HENDRICK International | 2016 - 2017

Accountable for office fitouts located at Sydney CBD, being the responsible for the safe, profitable and timely management of projects from commencement to completion. Further to this, I was the responsible by the budgeting of the project including cost estimates and quotations. With a proven ability in building strong relationships with internal stakeholders, clients and subcontractors, the project was delivered on time and with the highest quality standards

ASSISTANT SITE MANAGER I INTERN

PHV ENGENHARIA LTDA - | 2014 - 2015

Managing different projects and different parts of construction projects, supervising crew members, preparing estimates for time and material costs, completing quality assurance, observing health and safety standards, and compiling reports for different stakeholders. Working alongside various professionals and creating work schedules to meet project deadlines.

Working at four commercial towers projects listed below:

- Pavarotti Tower: responsible by the initial office fit outs of the new building.
- Irba Tower: team responsible for the finishing works and final deliver to customer
- Marcus de Mattos Tower: responsible for improving the speed and procedure of the structure's elevation
- Diamond Business Tower: team responsible for the finishing works and final deliver to customer

REFERENCES



RAMEL AMANOEL
LOGISTICS MANAGER
HANSON
0401 476 729
ramel_amanoel@hotmail.com



JASON BROWN
AREA MANAGER
HANSON
0488 901 581
jason.brown@hanson.com.au



DENNIS READ
MAINTENANCE MANAGER
HANSON
0419 243 907
dennis.read@hanson.com.au